## Muhammad Firdaus

#### Pelajar

Passionate and quick learning Software Engineer with 5 years of experience in computer science and software developing for wide range of projects and industries. seeking software development in all over the world to help increase software development efficiency.



Wonogiri, Central Java, Indonesia

# Pengalaman Kerja

## Front End Developer • PT GOTO Tbk

- Leading a team of frontend developers in the company's main product delivery.
- · Definition, description and distribution of tasks within the team.
- · Code review.
- Development, delivery and support of a mobile app using React Native.
- Investigation of product optimization possibilities.

Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

#### Back End Developer · PT Stockbit

Responsible for writing server-side web application logic. develop back-end components, connect the application with the other (often third-party) web services and support the front-end developers by integrating their work with the application.

Apr 2020 - May 2021

### Software Egineer • Apple Inc.

Assisted my team to develop the prototype of the concept for financial planning and analytics. Conducted research into new technology developed by the company to build the prototype. Tested the function, performance and possibility of the prototype with a real use case in business. Helped develop software that parses logs to analyze users' behavior of RapidResponse. Extended the feature of my employer's software to explore potential benefits for RapidResponse.

Jun 2022 - Now

# Pendidikan



Jun 2022 - Now

**SMK MUTUHARJO** 

**PPLG** 

### Skil

- HTML CSS
- JAVASCRIPT NodeJS
- JAVA KOTLIN FLUTTER

#### Bahasa

- Indonesian Professional
- English Professional